(Amy:)A comic that depicts a woman whose
bosom can't be used as a flotation device.
(Stuart:)Sorry. Most of the guys
who come in here like big boobs.
A couple of them have big boobs.
(Raj:)The new Warlords of Ka'a
expansion pack is out.
(Howard:)A new one? Unbelievable.
(Howard:)They just keep making up
more cheesy monsters...
(Howard:)...slapping them on cards
and selling them at 25 bucks a pop.
(Howard:)It's like a secret tax on guys
who can't get laid.
(Raj:)They're not even trying. Remember the
Satanimals pack with the Hellephant?
(Raj:)Absurd. What was he, a bad elephant
who died and went to hell?
(Raj:)What could an elephant possibly do that
would cause him eternal damnation?
"Wild West and Witches."
(Howard:)What kind of loser
cares about a showdown...
(Howard:)...between Billy the Kid
and the White Wizard of the North? Heh.
(Raj:)A total loser.
(Raj:)Obviously, a guy with a six-shooter
beats an old man with a magic wand.
Well, ho... hold on.
Uh, what if the wizard casts
a helmet-of-confusion spell...